Guide to the W. Sterling Cole papers M2023
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- AL Jay LeFevre to Cole, 1958 March 4; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Ray T. Lane, 1960 February 1; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Ray T. Lane, 1959 January 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Sergej Georgijewicz Lapin, 1958 February 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- Bulletin, "The Mitre Corporation of Lexington, Massachusetts", 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Bryan F. LaPlante, 1958 October 29; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Bryan F. LaPlante to Cole, 1958 October 27; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Bryan F. LaPlante to Cole, 1959 October 8; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- Note, "Biographical Data John B. Fisher." (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Eleanor I. Davisson to Cole, 1958 September 18; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Norman J. Learned to Cole, 1961 June 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- Newspaper articles, New York Herald Tribune, regarding the marriage of Mrs. Dickson, 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Norman J. Learned, 1961 June 9; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Norman J. Learned to Cole, 1961 May 29; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Norman J. Learned, 1960 January 18; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Norman J. Learned, 1959 July 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Robert LeBaron to Cole, 1958 October 15; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- AL LeBaron to Cole, 1958 June 21; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Sacher Hotel, 1958 June 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Robert LeBaron, 1958 June 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Mrs. Robert LeBaron to Cole, 1958 June 6; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS W. D. Leggett, Jr. to Cole, 1960 August 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- Telegram from Leggett to Cole, 1959 February 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS W.D. Leggett, Jr. to Cole, 1959 February 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS W.D. Leggett, Jr. to Cole, 1958 April 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Windsor Limited, 1961 August 28; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL C. Walter Rice to Cole, 1961 September 28; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS C. L. Cates to Cole, 1959 November 30; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to C.L. Cates, 1959 November 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS C.L. Cates to Cole, 1959 November 3; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Erwin Little, 1959 September 3; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Erwin Little, 1958 December 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Irwin Little, 1958 July 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- AL Little to Cole, 1958 June 23; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Erwin Little, 1958 April 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Allen P. Loohn to Cole, 1958 March 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Henry Lodge to Cole, 1959 June 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL D.G. Sullivan to Cole, 1959 May 15; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Chureed to Eddie, 1957 November 29; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL John W. Bricker to Cole, 1957 November 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Vernon Myers, 1961 March 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Vernon C. Myers to Cole, 1961 March; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Vernon C. Myers, 1960 March 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Vernon C. Myers to Cole, 1960 January; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Wm. E. Loomis, 1961 April 12; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS Mrs. Wm. E. Loomis to Cole, undated; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Helio Lopez to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TLS from Norris (mayor) to Cole, 1958 July 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- "M" (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Y.C. Mei, 1959 September 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Y.C. Mei, 1959 September 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Davis Merwin to Cole, 1959 October 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Davis Merwin, 1959 October 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Davis Merwin to Cole, 1959 August 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Metropolitan Club (Secretary W.J. DuBose) to Cole, 1961 April 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- List of members of the Metropolitan Club, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS W.J. DuBose to Cole, 1959 February 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to The Metropolitan Club, 1959 February 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to General Robert Cutler, 1958 November 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL L.S. to Cole, 1958 November 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Robert Cutler to Cole, 1958 November 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to E. Mettenet, 1960 April 20; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M. Michaels, 1961 February 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS M.I. Michaels to Cole, 1961 February 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS M.I. Michaels to Cole, 1961 February 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M.I. Michaels, 1961 February 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Note Unknown Sender to D.G., 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS J.C. Walker to Cole, 1960 September 14; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to A. Miller, 1961 January 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Arthur Miller to Cole, 1960 December 14; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to C.B. Miller, 1960 August 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- AL Mrs. Carl B. Miller to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Picture, "Baptismal Font, Mitchellsville Church", 1960 February 14 (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS A. Moljk to Cole, 1959 October 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to W. Miller, 1961 August 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to E. Moores, 1958 October 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Edward Moores to Cole, 1958 October 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Itinerary, Mr. and Mrs. E.A. Moores, 1958; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Morse, 1958 April 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS J.H. Morse, Jr. to Cole, 1958 March 18; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M. Michaels, 1960 April 2; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Telegram Cole to Edwin Plowden, 1957 December 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Lewis W. Morse to Cole, 1960 April 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Lewis Morse, 1960 April 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Jiri Hajek, 1958 April 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Dr. Pavel Winkler, 1958 April 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Program of visit of Director General of the International Atomic Energy Agency (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Airmail DonF. Musser to Cole, 1958 July 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Waldemar A. Nielsen to Cole, 1960 October 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Franklin A. Lindsay, 1960 September 28; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Franklin A. Lindsay to Cole, 1960 September 15; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Note regarding the change of address of Francis K. McCure, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Frank K. McCune to Cole, 1960 December 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Kazutaka Watanabe, 1961 February 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Charles H. Weaver to Cole, 1961 January 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Charles H. Weaver to Cole, 1960 December 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M. Mancuso, 1961 April 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Mary Mancuso to Cole, 1961 March 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Mike Mansfield, 1960 December 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Mike Mansfield, 1958 February 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS J.K. Mansfield to Cole, 1957 December 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Claude R. Morgeson, 1960 March 1; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- AL Claude R. Morgeson to Cole, 1960 February 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Julius Marmur, 1961 August 8; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Business card, Mildred Marmur (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Mrs. Julyius Maumur to Cole, 1961 July 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Joseph W. Marchtin, 1961 January 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Joseph W. Marchtin, Jr., 1961 January 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Mr. and Mrs. Seabury Mastick, 1959 January 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Seabury C. Mastick to Cole, 1960 January 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Majorie Mathews, 1959 May 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Charles W. Matthews, 1959 March 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Ormand Milton to Cole, 1961 April 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Ormand Milton to Cole, 1961 March 30; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Invoice, Airlift Services, 1961 March 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to L. Mendel Rivers, 1961 April 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Ormand Milton, 1961 April 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Telegram Cole to Mendel Rivers, 1961 March 1; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to L. Mendel Rivers, 1961 February 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M. Rivers, 1961 February 6; 1 correspondence (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Rivers to Cole, 1961 January 31 (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M. Rivers, 1961 January 9; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M. Rivers, 1960 November 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS M. Rivers to Cole, 1960 October 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Air Transportation: Movement of Traffic by the Single Manager Operating Agency for Airlift Service (MATS), 1959 November 5; 12 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to M. Rivers, 1960 November 30; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to S. Bingham, 1960 July 1; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Bingham to Cole, 1960 June 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- W. Carter to Cole: Airlift Service Billings, 1960 January 22; 9 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Earl C. Hedlund, Department of the Air Force, to Cole, 1959 December 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Hedlund to Cole, 1959 December 22 (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Francis O Wilcox, Assistant Secretary of State, to Cole, Washington, 1959 December 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Cole to Colonel Fischer, 1959 September 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Travel and excess baggage charges for Cole from Irvin a Fischer, 1959 August 18 (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Invoice to Cole, 1959 August 18; 9 invoices total (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Travel and Excess baggage charges to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Cole to Thomas Gates, 1959 August 13; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from William Bayse to Cole, 1959 May 11; 1 p. (3 copies) (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Bayse, 1959 April 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Wilcox to Cole, 1959 April 3; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Quarles to Wilcox, 1959 April 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Quarles to Vinson, 1959 March 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Robert Smart to Cole, 1959 April 3; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Smart, 1959 April 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Memorandum for Mr. Robert W. Smart, 1959 April 2 (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL from Cole to Carl Vinson, 1959 March 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Carl Vinson to Cole, 1959 February 24; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Vinson to McElroy, 1959 February 23; 3 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS to Russ Blandford from Cole, 1959 February 11; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Russ Blandford to Cole, 1959 January 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Francis Wilcox to Cole, 1958 December 16; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Bayse to Cole, 1958 December 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Raymond Winn to Mr. Wilcox, 1958 December 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Francis Wilcox to Cole, 1958 November 17; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Wilcox to McElroy, 1958 November 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Wilcox to Cole, 1958 October 30; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to Wilcox, 1958 October 29; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Copy of telegram, cc. Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL from Cole to Frank Everest, 1958 September 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL from Cole to Lillian Mayer, 1958 March 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Thomas McAndrew to Cole, 1960 July 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to McAndew, 1960 June 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to McAndrew, 1960 April 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Mc Andrew to Cole, 1959 December 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- Tom to Aunt and Uncle Stub (Cole), 1958 April 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to McAndrew, 1958 February 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McAndrew to Cole, 1958 February 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to McAnderw, 1958 February 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL from Cole to Stephen McClaran, 1958 February 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- ALS McClaran to Cole, 1958 December 12 (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Cole to McConaughy, 1958 July 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from John McCone to Cole, 1959 March 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McCone to Cole, 1959 January 10; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Ink to Cole, 1958 December 31; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to McCone, 1958 December 18; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Libby to Cole, 1958 December 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McCone to Cole, 1958 December 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McCone to Cole, 1958 December 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McCone to Cole, 1958 December 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Hall to Cole, 1958 November 6; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McCone to Cole, 1958 October 10; 3 pp. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Joseph McCroskey to Cole, 1959 May 4; 1 p. with newspaper clipping (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL from Cole to John McElduff, 1959 February 9 (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Harold McGraw to Cole, 1959 January 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL Cole to McGraw, 1959 January 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Murray to Cole, 1959 January 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS from Mac Innes to Cole, 1961 October 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL from Cole to Robert McKinney, 1961 October 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McKinney to Cole, 1961 October 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS McKinney to Cole, 1958 October 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS Eisenhower to McKinney (copy), 1958 October 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TLS J.F. Dulles to McKinney (copy), 1958 October 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- TL from Cole to Allan McKnight, 1961 October 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 359)
- "N" (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TL from Cole to President Nadjakov, 1960 September 30; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TL from Cole to Mr. Makicenovic, 1959 October 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TLS Gates to Cole, 1958 October 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TL Cole to Gates, 1958 September 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TLS from T.F. Cooper to Cole, 1957 November 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- Telegram from Cole to Robert J. Donovan, 1957 November 1; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TLS from Nichols to Cole, 1959 February 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TL Cole to Nichols, 1959 February 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TLS Nichols to Cole, 1959 February 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TL Cole to Nichols, 1968 October 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TLS Nichols to Cole, 1958 October 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TL Nichols to Cole, 1958 October 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TLS Nichols to Cole, 1958 October 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 360)
- TLS from C.L. Dive to Miss Pafavorth. (sp?), 1 p. and envelope (Box 6, Folder 360)
- "O" (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL from Cole to Mr. Wieser, 1960 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS American Express Company to Cole, 1960 March 30; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL American Express Company/Wieser to Cole, 1960 March 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Soucek, 1960 March 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Wieser, 1960 February 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL American Express to Cole, 1959 September 24; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS from Marne Obernauer to Cole, 1961 April 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Obernauer, 1961 August 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Obernauer, 1961 May 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Obernauer to Cole, 1961 May 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Obernauer, 1961 April 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Obernauer to Cole, 1961 March 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Obernauer, 1961 January 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Obernauer to Cole, 1960 April 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Obernauer to Cole, 1960 February 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Obernauer, 1959 September 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Obernauer to Cole, 1959 September 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Obernauer, 1958 February 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Obernauer to Cole, 1958 January 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS from Cole to Messrs. Ed. and Bill O'Brien, 1961 August 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS from H.L. Hoffman to Cole, 1958 October 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Hoffman to Cole, 1958 August 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to O'Brian, 1958 August 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS O'Brien to Cole, 1958 May 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS O'Brien to Cole, 1958 April 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to O'Brien, 1958 April 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Cole to O'Brien, 1958 March 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
  Resume attached.
- TL Cole to Ogden, 1960 June 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Ogden to Cole, 1960 June 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS from Janet Laung to Mary, 1960 April; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Porter, 1960 April 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Porter to Cole, 1960 April 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Porter to Cole, 1960 April 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL from Cole to Robert Oppenheimer, 1960 July 1; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Oppenheimer, 1960 June 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Oppenheimer to Cole, 1960 June 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Oppenheimer, 1960 May 16; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Hobson to Cole, 1960 April 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL from Cole to Robert Oppenheimer, 1960 April 11; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS from Robert Oppenheimer to Cole, 1960 May 2; 1 p. (3 copies) (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole toOppenheimer, 1960 April 11; 2 pp. (3 copies) (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL from Cole to Paul Jolles, 1958 April 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- Memorandum Jolles to Cole, 1958 April 4; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL from Cole to Andrew Martin, 1958 April 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Martin to Cole, 1958 March 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS from Sidney Phillips to D. Cole, 1958 April 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL D. Cole to Phillips, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Phillips to D. Cole, 1958 March 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS from Ward Canaday to Cole, 1958 December 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TL Cole to Ward, 1958 December 8; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Canaday to Cole, 1958 November 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- TLS Secretary to Canaday to Cole, 1958 October 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 361)
- "P" (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL from Cole to Erwin Felber, 1960 October 1; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Kemper to Cole, 1959 October 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL from Cole to Georges Delessert, 1958 September 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Delessert to Cole, 1958 September 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS from R. A. Patterson to Cole, 1960 March 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Patterson to Cole, 1958 July 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Patterson, 1958 July 30; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Patterson to Cole, 1958 July 24; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Patterson, 1958 July 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Patterson to Cole, 1958 July 14; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL from Cole to John L. Pauley, Jr., 1960 June 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Teague, 1960 June 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Teague to Cole, 1960 May 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS from John Pazourek to Cole, 1961 November 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS from Cole to Peanut Company, 1961 August 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to W.B. Peanut Company, 1959 July 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to W.B. Peanut Company, 1958 November 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to W.B. Peanut Company, 1958 November 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to W.B. Peanut Company, 1958 October 31; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to W.B. Peanut Company, 1958 October 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to W.B. Peanut Company, 1958 October 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to W.B. Peanut Company, 1958 April 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Crain (W.B. Peanut Company), undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS from Cole to Drew Pearson, 1959 August 10; 2 pp. (4 copies) (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL from Cole to Drew Pearson, 1957 October 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Pearson to Cole, 1957 October 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL from Cole to Emile Pelletier, 1961 October 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Pelletier to Cole, 1961 October 20; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
  (French and English)
- TL from Cole to Frederick de Hoffmann, 1961 April 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL from Cole to Charles Perry, 1961 November 15; 1 p. and newspaper clipping (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Perrys, 1961 February 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Perry, 1960 June 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Perry to Cole, 1961 May 31; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Perry, 1960 February 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Perrys and Marshalls, 1958 April 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- ALS Marshalls and Perrys to Coles, Monday; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Staatsoper Manager, 1958 February 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Hotel Lacher to Cole, 1958 March 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Ambassador Hotel, 1958 March 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Perry, 1958 February 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Perry to Cole, 1958 February 13; 1 p. and itinerary (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Cole to Ambassador Hotel (not sent), 1958 February 11; 1 p. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Perry, 1958 February 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Ambassador Hotel to Cole, 1958 February 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Ambassador Hotel, 1958 February 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Perry to Cole, 1958 February 5 (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Perry to Cole, 1957 December 9; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL H. Larsen to Cole, 1960 April 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Peter Justesen Co., 1960 April 12; 58 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
  Multiple billing statements, etc.
- AL Mrs. David K. Phemister to Cole, 1960 April 8; 3 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Pemester, 1960 January 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Colonel J.W. Knighton, 1958 February 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS J.W. Knighton to cole, 1958 January 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL J.W. Knighton to Cole, 1958 January 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Alfred N. Phillips to Cole, 1958 February 24; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to "Gentlemen" (USIS), 1958 November 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- Billing statements, 1957; 9 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- AL Evelyn and James Picker to Cole, 1959 January 15; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Fred Pitsley, 1958 October 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS E. Plowden to Cole, 1957 December 30; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Fletcher Plumley, 1959 January 8; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to The President of the Police, 1959 May 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Dwight J. Porter, 1961 February 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Dwight J. Porter to Cole, 1961 January 31; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Unknown Sender to Paul R. Jolles, 1959 January 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Melvin Price to Cole, 1959 February 14; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Melvin J. Price, 1959 February 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Mrs. R.R. Poulton, 1961 July 24; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Raymond Poulton, 1961 July 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- AL Cole to Raymond Poulton, undated; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Winston L. Prouty, 1958 February 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TLS Winston L. Prouty to Cole, 1958 February 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- TL Cole to Morawa & Co., 1959 February 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- Translation Note Cole to Morawa & Co., undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)